orderwave.com 2006-09-07

# Orderwave | Inventory Management, Order Automation, Payment Processing, Shopping Cart, and more.

Orderwave: Privacy Policy 

1\. Information Collection and Use  
DRG Intelligent Computer Concepts, Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on orderwave.com. DRG Intelligent Computer Concepts, Inc. collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

We store information that we collect through cookies and log files. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the user’s personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user’s visit to our Web site, and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them. We do not share your profile with other third parties. 

Cookies  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s hard drive for an extended period of time. If users reject the cookie, they may not enjoy full functionality of the site. 

Log Files  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are tied to personally identifiable information to enable our Web-based service. 

2\. Communications from the Site  
Newsletter  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections.

Service Announcements  
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature. 

Customer Service  
We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes.

Sharing  
Legal Disclaimer  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

Choice/Opt-out  
Our users are given the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for information

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the “Opt Out” link in the email.

3\. Security  
This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information such as credit card number and/or social security number, that information is encrypted and is protected with SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just ‘surfing’.

If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can send an email to support@4icc.com. 

4\. Supplementation of Information   
In order for this Web site to properly fulfill its obligation to users it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources.

Enhancement of Marketing Profile  
We purchase third party marketing data and add it to our existing user database to better target our advertising and provide pertinent offers we think our users would be interested in. We use this information to enhance or overlay the ‘profile’ of individual users. This aggregate marketing data is therefore tied to the users’ personally identifiable information. See also the “Profile.”

4\. Notification of Changes  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

If, however, we are going to use users’ personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices. 

5\. Contact Information  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:

310-217-4700   
310-217-4766  
20102 S. Vermont Ave.  
Torrance, CA 90502  
www.orderwave.com
